https://www.raincode.com/privacy-policy

1000 Brussels – BELGIUM
Our website address is: https://www.raincode.com, the website is fully hosted by Siteground. We use WordPress as content management system.
What personal data we collect and why we collect it
When visitors fill in a contact form on the site, we collect the data shown in the contact form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help with spam detection.
What information do we store?
We store user input data sent through the contact forms on this website (First Name, Last Name, Company , Country, Phone Number, Email, Message, along with meta information about the submissions, including the time stamp, the origin IP address, original referrer, landing page and the user agent [browser]).
Where does the information go?
We use the Contact Form 7 plugin to manage contact form submissions. The information is sent as email messages that only a select few are allowed to access. The information is also stored in the database of Phidani Software SPRL, on their hosting server for backup and later reference purposes.
A copy of the submission information is stored in our in-house database. Our Customer Relation Management system, which is hosted by us, has access to these informations.
How long do you keep the information?
We don’t set a particular time limit on storing information because we need it for future reference. If you want your information to be removed from our database, please contact us (info[@]raincode.com) . We will remove it anytime there are concerns about your privacy.
Do you share the information with other parties?
We share our database with others companies from the SlashKernel group (legal name Phidani Software SPRL).
Anonymised data
We use Google Analytics, heatmap.me and WP Statistics to collect anonymized data which allows us to have general statistics about our website traffic.
Download Free COBOL Compiler
First Name (required)
Last Name (required)
Email* (required)
*Use of a professional email address entitles you to 3 hours of FREE technical support.
Company (required)
Country (required)
Do you have a mainframe (required)
YesNo
Do you use Visual Studio (required)
YesNo
I authorize Raincode to store my submitted information to respond to my inquiry. See Privacy Policy
I authorize Raincode to store my submitted information to respond to my inquiry.See Privacy Policy
I authorize Raincode to store my submitted information to respond to my inquiry. See Privacy Policy
Not just a limited version, not for a limited time, and not as a development or runtime license only.
It’s just free!
Even if you use it for an application that you sell thousands of copies of.
Even if you have hundreds of developers in-house.
Generates thread-safe, 100% managed code for .NET 3.5, 4.0 or 4.5 in 32 and 64-bit mode
Supports mainframe COBOL syntax
2013, 2015 & 2017 Visual Studio® plugin with Intellisense® support
Native support for SQL and CICS®
Azure Ready
No license fees. Not now, not ever.
Just fill in the form and get your free COBOL compiler!
First Name (required)
Last Name (required)
Email* (required)
*Use of a professional email address entitles you to 3 hours of FREE technical support.
Company (required)
Country (required)
Do you have a mainframe (required)
YesNo
Do you use Visual Studio (required)
YesNo
I authorize Raincode to store my submitted information to respond to my inquiry. See Privacy Policy
I authorize Raincode to store my submitted information to respond to my inquiry. See Privacy Policy
I authorize Raincode to store my submitted information to respond to my inquiry.See Privacy Policy
I authorize Raincode to store my submitted information to respond to my inquiry.See Privacy Policy
I authorize Raincode to store my submitted information to respond to my inquiry. See Privacy Policy
I authorize Raincode to store my submitted information to respond to my inquiry.See Privacy Policy
I authorize Raincode to store my submitted information to respond to my inquiry.See Privacy Policy
I authorize Raincode to store my submitted information to respond to my inquiry.See Privacy Policy
I authorize Raincode to store my submitted information to respond to my inquiry.See Privacy Policy
I authorize Raincode to store my submitted information to respond to my inquiry. See Privacy Policy
×
CLOSE
Request Technical Deep Dive
×
